Trying to make a smooth transition.
Damn it!
I misclicked, guys.
I ruined the whole intro.
I was gonna do something so epic with it, too.
Like, you don't even understand.
I had this all planned out and everything.
What?
I'm streaming.
I'm doing it now.
Okay.
Okay, I gotta hurry.
I... I can't explain.
I gotta stream.
I don't have long, okay?
It's gonna be a shorter one.
I don't have long.
Here we go.
Let's do this.
Dude, there's been like 15 strangers in my home today.
Coming in and out and I can't stop it.
I think I got it under control, though.
It's so weird.
Let's go.
Check it out.
All of these are locked.
Minus 12 win streak!
I guess we can try to unlock more of those.
My theory is that we just need to do the same thing, but on different characters.
So, maybe we do that.
Maybe we bring in Isaac.
Isaac!
Let's do it.
I wanna do Isaac right now.
Not like that, but you know.
Curse of darkness, what?
What a start.
Let me... there we go.
Okay, I'm ready.
I'm streaming, I'm doing it, I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
Don't worry.
Yes, yes, I know the script.
Yes, I lose the first one, I get it.
Sorry.
Here we go.
There we go.
Nothing to bomb, that's too bad.
What?
Oh, I need to make a joke later, right?
Nevermind.
Oh, you heard that?
Sorry.
I don't know, I don't have long guys.
I'm really trying here.
Come on.
Easy, no problem.
Dude, I cleaned my house today.
My apartment, I mean.
But like, we're talking deep clean, you know?
Like, really deep clean.
The type of clean where I woke up at eight and cleaned until three.
It feels amazing.
God, I love that feeling.
Wait, I go back.
Treasure room is calling.
Here.
Hmm, I can bomb my way in here.
Not that it does anything, but you know.
It's fun.
Okay, let's remember this.
We have the D6, we can potentially reroll things.
Not in here though, because it's only for pedestals, right?
Pedestal items in the room.
But this one is a pedestal item, actually.
I just don't have any money for it, so, you know.
Would be nonsensical to reroll that.
Ooh, I like this one.
We're taking this one.
How come I'm not getting any shitty ones, man?
So I can reroll.
I'm getting too many good items.
Like, the last time I had Isaac, this same thing happened.
Whoa, is it gonna fart in my face?
No, please don't do it.
Okay, it's the harmless fart.
We're not worried about that.
I could go in there.
I'm gonna do it.
Whoa!
Oh, check this out.
Actually, that was not really the plan.
But sure.
It's fine.
We're gonna reroll the boss item.
There's also...
It's fine.
I actually have a lot of keys.
Just play patient against this guy.
No reason to lose your head.
This guy is so easy, actually.
One of the easier bosses, for sure.
Mom's heels, nice.
Wait, I forgot I could reroll, but I think this is good, actually.
I do want this item.
Yes, this is a good item, actually.
That's fine.
Range is good, damage is good, you know?
Like, all of that.
Also, wait a minute, how do I have...
Oh, because I got the Stigmata, right?
I was like, how do I have 4 health?
Duh, obviously.
Oh, no!
No, not like that!
I lost my Demon Chance!
I forgot I had to be careful immediately.
Almost inattentive.
It happens.
Oh, no, we're lost.
There's still a chance, guys.
36%, huh?
There's still a chance.
Yeah.
Did you see that?
I ran into the...
It's the first game, it's a warm-up.
It's expected.
Okay, let's just get rid of that guy.
Ohoy!
Nice.
Good dodge on that.
Okay, okay.
Can I just win the first one?
Fine, I'll lose it.
Don't worry about that.
I gotta stick to the script here, guys.
Apparently, it's good for, you know, the numbers or whatever.
I don't really think about it too much.
I just do what he's telling me.
Do you think I could make the soundtrack for this game with my voice?
I think I could.
Bloodshot eye!
Uh, you know what?
I hate it.
Reroll!
Fuck!
I regret.
I don't really want that.
Then again, I mean, I have no bombs.
Maybe it's okay?
Nah, I want to reroll that.
I'll be back.
That was like a shit item to get, honestly.
It's like a boring item too, you know?
10 bombs, wow.
Hey!
Just in time!
Too bad it's too late for the buffer now.
Uh, man, can we even get enough battery?
To do this again?
I don't think we can.
At this point, I think we're kind of cooked.
Boss is there.
Maybe there's a battery in these poops.
I may as well go in here.
You should die until you die from it.
Come here.
Oh, man.
Good.
I mean, this...
Oh, we're gonna go for the cheese!
Configuration.
I almost had it, I almost had it.
We gotta go up here and then like that.
Cheese configuration has been achieved!
Thank you very much, thank you.
Thank you.
Beautiful.
Look at that.
What?
Dude, what is it with these absolute dog shit items I'm getting today?
I want to re-roll two of these now!
Well, dang it.
Uh, have I been here?
I have.
Have I been here?
No.
Okay.
Maybe we can get enough battery just for one more re-roll, perhaps?
That would please me.
You want to come over here?
Come on.
Whoa, what the fuck is that?
Hold on.
Grants a 22% chance to revive as question mark upon death?
Wait, you mean, uh, Bibi?
What the frick?
How did that happen, Oliver?
I'm so disappointed in myself.
Like, that is just...
That cannot happen like that.
That I love.
Can we get it?
Then again, buying this for the buffer for the next floor could also be huge.
Huh?
Maybe that's better to do, actually.
There's no way I'm getting three batteries groups.
What am I saying?
Battery... levels?
I don't know what the fucking word is for that.
Battery stacks.
Stacks of levels?
I don't know.
Whatever.
We're lost.
Nice, there's more rooms.
It's not over yet.
Wow.
Wow!
Why am I going to a corner?
It's a bad idea.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Okay, I think I have to go in here.
For that battery.
Sick.
What's that?
Yo!
Awesome!
One more battery needed.
Oh, we're gonna get it, that's awesome.
The question is, what am I gonna re-roll?
I think I'm gonna re-roll the 10 bombs, because...
Come on.
I would rather have the cards than the bombs.
If I'm really lucky here, I can get four coins.
But I would have to be really lucky.
It's not happening.
Shit.
Three bombs though, we could look for secret rooms.
Let me try and calculate this, so left is good.
Up is good.
Uh, let me see this here.
Ooh, this could be it.
Fuck.
Uh, man, I wish I could see the map.
Also, where's my treasure room item?
Is it up here?
It was.
Reroll this crap.
That's good!
I'm not sad about that.
That brings me happiness.
Now we're gonna go down to the shop.
We're gonna grab this thing here.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe we're gonna look for a secret room first.
Oh, come on.
I'm gonna save my last bomb.
We got two blue hearts as buffered now.
We are set for the third floor.
Uh, no.
Yeah.
What do we get?
Blood donation.
Ooh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on.
This is the money I need.
Oh, why didn't I take this first?
Chariots.
Ooh.
Dude!
We can do it.
Uh, let's go down to...
Is this risky?
One red heart.
Uno, reto, harto.
Ooh!
Wait, it's a fucking active.
Shit.
Oh, well.
I'm gonna duplicate the shit out of this now.
Two of diamonds.
Eighteen coins.
And then we're taking...
Uh, I guess this one.
Back to the shop.
Oh, this is so sick.
Um, I think it was here?
No.
Here?
Fuck.
That was the treasure room.
There it is.
Okay, uh, we take this, right?
Show me the goods.
Wait, twenty?
Fifty-five for placebo.
Yeah, how about no?
No, thanks.
I am intrigued by the rune, though.
Could blow this guy up to potentially get a bit more money and get this.
But, uh, I'm not, uh, I'm not sold on this.
Nope.
Wish I had twenty bucks, though.
It is what it is.
This was good.
Solid.
Man, this is a great second floor.
Now we just gotta not take too much damage, otherwise the run is over.
So I gotta be really careful.
Uh, plus two damage.
I think I'd rather have that, actually.
I think that's more worth it.
Yeah.
Plus two damage.
Also, the plan is we're gonna get to the strange door.
And see what happens when we play Isaac.
We're gonna get to the end with Isaac.
A hundred percent demon chance.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Who are you?
Dude, how much HP do you have?
Ooh!
Sick!
I hate that I can't see my HP.
But so far we haven't lost any, so...
Oh, almost just lost some, though.
Wow!
More range?
At least I can see the map.
Sick!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Uh, let's go here.
Let's keep that in mind, but later.
Oh my god.
Yo!
No!
Okay, so we have one red heart and one and a half blue hearts right now.
This is the status.
Good.
Go down here.
Wow.
Okay, so we have three red hearts.
One of them is filled.
One and a half blue.
That's what happens when you take risks.
Get away from me.
Oh, come on.
Give me some healing, man.
You guys got a job with me?
Okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So we currently have one blue, one red.
Money.
Nice.
Dude, how about you give me like a room here, like treasure room or shop or something?
The hell is going on here?
Come on.
These guys are annoying as hell.
They're stacked up though.
This is nice for me.
Line him up, as day nine would say.
When the blue flame hellians roll in.
This is nice.
That was a great little ending there to that encounter.
Okay, I have somehow just avoided all the good rooms.
Just kind of amazing.
You're gonna come over here.
Just keep moving.
You know what's tricky about these guys?
When they shoot, your instinct is to dodge, and then you walk right into one of those, you know?
Because they shoot a split.
I can't get across here.
Okay.
Dude, both of the good rooms are right here.
That's kind of crazy.
What do you do, sir?
Yo, healing is good.
Two red hearts, one blue.
Two and a half red hearts.
What is that?
Number one.
Plus tiers?
Less range?
Tears turn yellow and fire from lower.
I have a lot of range, so I think this is actually good.
This is going to significantly increase my DPS.
Solid upgrade.
Don't really like any of this.
Let's see what's downstairs.
Wait, show me the description for this.
Show me.
Why is it showing me?
Ah, fuck.
Okay.
We can get our range back and get one more out of Yes, Mother.
If we get enough money, of course.
And we have a question mark rune.
Both are intriguing.
This one is also very intriguing, the middle one, but I just don't understand what it does.
It feels useless so far.
I mean, it's obviously not, I imagine, but, you know.
Let's do the boss.
We still have 100% demon.
So if we get a demon rune, assuming we don't take damage, we're going to be able to re-roll it if we don't get what we want.
And what do we want?
Say it with me.
Brimstone!
Yes!
That's good.
Good job.
That's what we want.
Here we go.
Gertie Jr. This is the one that's going to blast me, isn't it?
Die right into the booth!
What's wrong with me?
Kill that guy.
Oh, wow.
Okay, I can take one more hit.
I think.
Oh, yo, yo, yo.
Put down the goyo.
Shit.
Get him, get him.
Nice.
That was close.
Yeah, that's nice.
I like that one.
That's actually huge.
Oh, no.
Hate it.
Oh, I don't know what this is, but look, it's a bomb.
Actually, I know what it is.
This is definitely the bomb that makes Brimstone in each direction.
I just know it without even having seen it.
I know it.
We're going to re-roll this shit.
Damn it.
Ah, that's not bad either.
That's a good one.
Oh, actually, hold on.
Both are kind of good.
But that means if I do this, I have no red hearts and then...
No, I can't do it.
I got to take this and move on.
Platesafe.
Dude, look at my attack speed now.
This is actually sick.
Not bad.
Kind of want to explore more.
Just in case I find more money, I also have this golden key that I want to utilize.
Maybe find some secret rooms while we're at it.
Oh, oh, oh, I forgot about this.
I could have potentially re-rolled again to get a Brimstone.
Shit.
You know what I should do?
I should, every time I see something like this, I should write down on a notepad.
Like, you know how pilots have a checklist before they take off?
We should write a checklist for this floor.
Before the end boss, you know, so I always check the things.
So I write these checklists down or check marks every time I see one of these things I want to do, you know?
Nice.
Show me the money.
No money?
Okay, I'm gonna be a little bold here.
Okay, okay.
It's fine, it's fine.
One more.
Dick!
Let's do one more.
Uno mas, uno mas.
Shit.
I want pills so bad.
Like, I can't even explain to you how much I want to consume those pills.
Whoa.
Here, these guys are kind of tanky and I have a lot of DPS.
Okay.
Get feared, nerd.
Another one?
Okay.
I mean, it's really unnecessary, but okay.
Like, how do you even react to that?
He jumped at Mach 9.
Fucking crazy.
Okay.
11 coins.
So right now, I have a blue heart.
The black heart is gone, right?
We saw that.
So if I go in there, we're gonna lose the full blue heart and we're back to red hearts.
And I don't think I like that because we're currently at two red hearts.
So we have two red hearts, one blue.
We can't do it.
Can't do it, captain.
Moving on.
There's a card up there.
What was that one?
I could still get this if I wanted.
It may not be worth it, actually.
Let me see what's in here again.
Wait, did I ever check this out?
I did, right.
You know what?
I think I will buy this.
We gotta experiment with it, right?
Like, it's gotta do something.
I'm gonna try and really pay attention.
Um, that's it.
That's it.
We're done here.
Let's get out.
Straight down.
Cheers.
I would say this is a solid first run.
Catacombs.
No curses.
Nice.
Oh, we have two blue hearts.
I thought we had one.
Let's see what it is.
Damn.
That's actually kind of brutal.
That takes me below one in speed.
I feel like I should have more damage.
Like, my stats are saying one thing and then my experience is different.
Wait, how did I just get those flies?
Could that be the heart?
I'm trying to just spitball things right now.
That was interesting.
Now the flies are gone.
Oh,
yeah, I got flies again.
Could be the thing.
I mean, then again, it could also be a million other things.
Another one.
Okay, we currently have a pretty good demon chance.
I think I should just go in.
We also have the d6 ready.
Yeah, let's do it.
Oh, this guy's tough though.
You could kick my ass.
I can't believe I just ran into that.
Jesus.
I'm not going to jump all the way from there, right?
We got him.
Sick.
Constellation prize.
This is most definitely going to give me speed.
Maybe it's okay.
It's also going to give me a bomb, right?
I think I don't like it.
I would rather get an HP.
I mean, okay.
Okay.
It's, you know, money.
I'll come back.
Let's just say I'll come back with more battery.
I kind of want him to blow up the wall here.
Shoot me.
I'll shoot me over here.
This is optimized gameplay, people.
Pay attention.
Take notes.
Okay, so I think he hit me over there.
Come on, sir.
He gets feared when he gets too close.
Dude, what are you doing?
Come on.
Get over here.
Okay.
If you're over there, I may as well try over there.
I think that would have actually destroyed the wall here, but I'm not inside.
Now he's over there.
Dude.
Okay.
I've had it with you.
There we go.
Hey, two soul hearts.
Yay.
That's kind of massive.
I almost walked on the spikes.
I could do this, but that's my last bomb, so I think not.
I reject the idea.
Dude, I cheese-configurated him.
A brief moment there.
Sick range.
Yeah.
No.
Oh my god.
That's so scary.
I think I got it, though.
When I saw those spiders, my heart stopped.
Don't take my battery.
Imagine.
No, thanks.
Let's go back and re-roll now.
Let's do... yeah, this way.
I need, like, if I can get one more HP, I need a health item.
I feel like the boss item pool has a pretty high chance of spawning a health plus item.
Okay, that's good, too.
Honestly, like, even more attack rate.
It's nice.
It's good damage.
I'm actually just keep the map up.
Oh, I almost stepped on the spikes.
Yeah, keep up the map like this, and then we're just gonna walk.
Go this way.
Dude, my character looks crazy.
We have this metal plate in our head, and we look like a freaking demon.
Look, damage is really good here.
There's like a weird... you see how it's, like, doubling my attack sometimes?
It's not a consistent fire rate.
I think it's related to the left eye, right eye stuff.
Let me see this thing.
Yeah, see?
Increases fire rate from Isaac's left eye.
Oh, that's good!
I like that.
Definitely taking that.
That's just a straight up damage reduction item, in a way.
I'm too spooky for you.
Boom.
Hey, you know what?
Come here and blow this up.
Damn.
Wouldn't that have been beautiful?
I can almost get that.
No.
Let's see what's down here.
Pulse worm.
19 for this one?
I don't know about that.
I'm immediately attracted to the humbling bundle.
Yeah.
Like, that's just solid, you know?
I can definitely find two coins.
I could even step in the step room, if I needed to.
There's also one more room.
That was minus speed.
Aha!
Yeah, well, I can't do that.
Shit.
Maybe I can't find the money.
Maybe here?
No.
I think we're cooked.
I may have to step to do it.
It's not worth it.
I'm gonna save my money.
Could get the blue heart, I guess.
Ah, I think it's okay.
Yeah, let's get out of here.
Although, if I blow this up, I could get coins.
Do it!
Okay.
Well, it's not actually the worst.
We could look for a secret room now.
Somewhere in the center, right?
I think... somewhere over here.
Like, right here is a perfect... Look, it even has, like, a connection there.
How much you want to bet it's there?
Fuck.
Okay, how much you want to bet it's here?
Okay, we're leaving.
Now, I have no keys.
Damn it.
Why does this always happen?
Let's just cut our losses and get out.
I've done enough damage.
All right, watch this.
We're gonna blow this up.
We're gonna get a plus one health.
Okay, good enough.
Good enough.
Imagine that was a plus one health.
Honestly, the more tiers we get at this point, it's gonna stack up faster and faster and faster, right?
I mean, obviously, but I'm saying it's gonna get crazier the more we get.
And that's obvious, too.
I don't know why I'm pointing this out.
You know this.
Yeah, fuck.
I panic.
That was a panic.
Two blue hearts.
Oh, man, how did I dodge that?
That was crazy.
Freaking gravity in here.
Bombs are nice.
Got no keys, though.
Oh, the red fire!
That's a red flame.
Alert, alert, alert.
I could have been hit by that.
No, don't do that to me.
We gotta find Hank, man.
This is the guys that jump, right?
Shit.
Oh, what the... Fear me.
Fear me.
I'm too spooky for you.
Oh, you bastard!
It is okay.
I hate these floating heads.
They're harder to deal with when they're alone.
My creatures...
You know what?
This is better.
You know why?
Because I don't intend to die.
You gotta stay positive and aim for the greats, you know?
Keeping that other thing is just... Whoa, that was kind of crazy.
Yeah, it doesn't make sense to keep the other thing unless you plan on dying, right?
Nice.
That was actually very important that we got that key.
Especially since we have this here, but I'm gonna save it for the treasure room.
Curse of the Tower.
I don't know, actually.
I don't think I want that.
Maybe I'll come back depending on what I find, but yeah.
Right now, I'm not feeling it.
See?
My mask actually prevented me from taking damage just there.
You saw that?
Destroy poop, spawn a blue attack fly.
Ah, that's also kind of good.
That's a trinket, right?
Yeah.
Let's do this one.
I need to find a treasure room.
Shit.
Oh my god.
Too spooky for you is saving me.
Hey, hey, hey.
Get away from me.
South.
Oh no, this stuff.
Go!
Wow.
It's spooky.
Too spooky for me.
Oh, okay.
Careful.
Come
on, the nerds.
Bring it on.
Gonna charge me or something?
Get spooked.
He doesn't get spooked.
Dude, he's spawning a lot.
Oi, oi, oi.
Oh.
Ah, tricky enemy.
There's the treasure room.
Wait, where's the other guy?
Oh, he died.
What is that?
Technology zero.
Tears of small beams of electricity that arc between them.
Whoa, I like that.
Oh, that sounds, yo.
That's awesome.
So wait, if I look at, look at that.
Holy shit, dude.
That's awesome.
Wait, does it actually do any more damage though?
I guess it's better for AOE.
I think I prefer Jacob's ladder.
So far.
Definitely looks stronger than it is.
But pretty cool.
I'm scared, mom.
Okay.
Here's the... Wait, where the hell is the treasure room?
Oh wait, we already had the treasure room.
What about second treasure room?
We're taking the boss now.
I forgot what these guys do.
Oh, okay.
My mask just helped me.
Okay, okay.
No, fuck!
Don't take my demon chance.
Don't take my demon chance!
No!
The fuck?
Oh shit!
Oh my god!
Jewel, baby!
I want this one.
I want range.
Wait, I already have good range.
I gotta save my reroll for the angel.
I'm taking this.
Oh, what the frick?
Oh no, don't do this to me.
I don't know what it is.
I really want a reroll, but I gotta take it.
I gotta take it.
Monstrance, purifying light.
Rants a large golden aura that deals damage to enemies within it.
Enemies take more damage from the aura the closer they are to its center.
Wait, I've had this before.
How come it wasn't... Maybe I got it in greed mode or something, or challenge.
I forgot which one of those makes it so that I don't actually get it.
I could fight the dude, but I'm not gonna fight the dude.
Instead, I'm gonna grab the loot, and we're gonna move on.
Okay.
May blow these up.
Come on, please.
Buffer me!
Okay, fine.
I'm gonna save my last.
Also, I'm gonna go...
Yeah, we got 17 coins.
We gotta go to the shop.
Before we leave, definitely.
I still have a reroll.
Maybe I can use that there.
But there's also the other item we found, actually.
I could also reroll that.
Man, I really wish I could get in there and grab that.
Right now, that would be so cool.
Actually, it wouldn't help me too much, because it's just gonna give me one heart.
Oh!
I didn't even plan that.
That was actually kind of risky.
I could reroll this, I think.
But that's gonna replace my...
Ooh!
Ah, but then I don't have money for the thing.
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We got a kit downstairs.
Let's see what we got here.
What the hell is that?
Equality.
Grants a large fire rate increase when collected coins, bombs, and keys are all equal.
Nah.
It's never gonna happen.
64?
Consumes key pickups from the ground and spawns random chests?
I mean, I guess that's good, but is it 64 good?
Ooh, I don't know about that.
I say no to that.
I think I'm gonna take the school back, because the D6 I always want to keep.
You know what, actually, before I do, let's see what I get here.
Marked!
Tears automatically fire at a crosshair on the...
Ah, I don't know about that.
I mean, we have to go mouse mode, then.
Actually, hold on, let me see.
Oh, okay, let's try that.
Let's just experiment with the mouse on that one.
I like it.
We're gonna grab this.
I keep saying this, and then I'm gonna regret going mouse mode, because it's just so unintuitive for me.
But we're gonna try it.
We're gonna try it.
No secret rooms found.
We have one bomb.
Let's not get hit by this.
I'm kind of scared.
Maybe I...
Dude, I'm too scared.
Maybe there's a secret room right below me here?
Please!
Okay, we go.
That was so close.
Wow.
I just realized, even if I had gotten access to a secret room, it wouldn't have actually done anything, because I still needed a bomb to get through the other side.
Well, you know, it happens.
Don't get hit by anything.
Yeah, all the way down.
Oh, I wish it would stop shooting.
Like, can you just do it when I hold my button, please?
But okay.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, grant me Sokka.
And an extra heart.
And then we really need to start working on more health, because this is absolutely despicable.
We need a Black Bible is what we need.
And we need a teleport on this floor.
We may not get it.
Dude, I can't play like this.
God, I gotta go keyboard, I think.
No, let's just give it another shot.
If I had more attack speed, this would be better.
Like, there's too much delay between where I aim and when my stuff arrives, you know?
Or not attack speed, shot speed.
Okay, more range is good, I guess.
Oh, you're right.
Control cancels it.
Good.
No, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna use my keyboard for this.
Fuck the mouse.
We're going back to keyboard.
I have decided.
It's like, honestly, I'm not happy about picking this up at all.
No, I hate it.
Mouse, back to mouse.
Keyboard sucks on this for sure.
Dude, I fucked my build.
I don't like what I got here.
It's terrible.
What is this crazy room?
I have no damage.
Nah, dude, I'm totally cooked.
My mom, I ruined my build.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Dude.
Uh, go here.
There we go.
I need to...
Man, this V6 has not seen a lot of mileage.
Oh, god.
Don't charge me.
Is that a chance to heal a red hard?
Sure.
No, no, I want this.
Ah, man, I don't like any of this.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god.
Dude, I am so bad at this.
It's crazy.
Yikes!
Wow.
Actually, maybe I just go back and forth like this, because it's like electricity, right?
So I just go like this.
That way I can hit...
Oh, dude, actually.
Maybe that's the play here.
Because they're arcing, right?
Unlike that.
Dude, treasure room?
Okay, we can do this now.
No, wait, not just...
I hate myself.
Objectives have changed.
We are in survival mode now.
This is all about winning.
Any way we can.
I mean, what are the chances I would have gotten?
Oh, wait, I'm dead!
You know what?
I'm happy with that.
I hated my build anyway at the end.
Like, the whole mouse control shit.
Eww, terrible.
I don't like it.
Absolutely horrible.
Uh...
Let's go with...
Let's do Eden.
I like Eden.
And then I think after that, we're gonna do, uh...
The newest Azel.
Because I'm already, uh...
Fending for that.
Pyromaniac!
That's nice!
D6!
It's a very good setup.
One red heart, two blue.
I like it.
Oh god!
Nerd.
Suck.
Thank you very much.
Already, I like this build better.
Than the build I had last run.
And we haven't even gone through two rooms yet.
Now we gotta find, uh...
Norman Reedus.
With a fetus.
That will complete the build.
Let me in.
We got a buffer as well.
Let's take care of that buffer and not lose it.
Very important.
Oh wait, we have Curse of whatever the fuck is going on right now.
No, no, no, no!
I said take care of the buffer.
This room is actually insane.
This is unbelievably difficult!
Holy room!
Wow!
Shit!
Nice!
Oh, I'm rich!
Rich get richer!
Back to the shop.
Got that.
Cash!
I'm thinking voodoo head.
Maybe.
We can also save it for the next shop.
Yeah, you know what?
Let's save it for the next shop.
I'm not the biggest fan of voodoo head.
Then again, I mean, the rewards are nice, right?
But are they that nice?
I think it's better when you don't have all these buffers, you know?
If I had a lot of red hearts, I would do it.
But I don't.
Or if I could fly, you know?
Speaking of flies.
Okay, we're gonna do the boss now.
Maybe re-roll.
In fact, the earlier the better, because then I will be able to have more rooms to clear to get more battery.
For a potential second re-roll, you know?
Boom!
Calculated.
Oh no, are you kidding me?
Again?
Now we're talking.
Heh heh.
Good shit.
Okay, time to look for the treasure room.
Sup, guys?
Is this for you?
Oh, that was juicy.
I couldn't resist.
We have so many bombs.
You gotta have fun, right?
Also, hold on, hold on!
I almost forgot!
This heals me!
I was like, oh yeah, I'm immune!
But it... it heals me!
It's even better than I remember.
So, you know, we're actually kinda...
Dude, we're actually cooking right now.
We need to...
Maybe we need to save the bombs more.
Hero Maniac is like...
a freaking S++ item.
I can't even explain how good it is.
I feel like it speaks for itself.
No items?
Okay, treasure room acquired, though.
Oh, that's a good one!
Nice!
I'm not gonna re-roll that.
That is solid.
We're done.
See, I said I wouldn't be spending my bombs, but I am gonna look for secret rooms.
I think this one...
doesn't get more centralized than that.
Fuck yeah!
How good am I?
Oh, okay.
That was kind of an underwhelming secret room.
I didn't like that.
May not even have been worth it for that one bomb.
See, now I really need to find some health up items.
Because, otherwise, my Pyro Maniac is gonna be kinda wasted.
Can't heal blue hearts, right?
Gotta get red hearts.
Oh no, I can't see my HP.
This is so annoying right now.
Dude, I'm one-shotting these tiny poops.
Good damage!
Dude, I have seven damage right now!
This is very good.
I can't squander this.
This is my moment!
We also gotta look for a teleport card.
This is the other objective we have.
And tinted rocks.
Let's look for those.
Curse room there.
Yeah,
go left.
Oh, money poop!
Tell me my rich get richer theory is incorrect.
It's not.
Chance to gain one additional cent each time you pick up a coin, that's massive.
Especially because it means we can probably buy some bombs later.
Okay, we have a hundred percent demon.
I may actually not do the demon.
I think I'm gonna save up for Angel.
Even though we have re-roll, I'm gonna use it to get a health up item from the boss pool.
This guy is not too bad, actually.
I like it.
Okay, it's not health up.
I'm gonna re-roll it.
Even though this is very good, I'm gonna re-roll it.
I'll come back and re-roll it again.
Shit.
Wait, what the hell?
Didn't even see that chest.
Huh, alright.
Wait, I have to remember, the bombs from the enemies heal me too, I keep avoiding them.
I really shouldn't, I should be embracing them.
It's just so foreign to me to walk into a bomb, you know, like my mind can't.
I get used to that.
It feels wrong on so many levels.
Let's get that battery going here.
I'm walking into a corner.
69.
After taking damage, all additional damage in the room is reduced to... that's nice.
That is the poor man's wafer.
Very good.
More options, it's fantastic as well.
I'm taking that.
We have a battery we can buy, may not be needed.
Let's wait.
We can potentially do two re-rolls here, if we play it right.
Ha!
Or three re-rolls!
Now, we need one more battery, man, one more room, come on.
Look for a secret room.
It's gotta be possible, right?
It's not here.
Let me really think about this.
Wait, was there something on the left up here?
There was, so it can't be there.
Okay, got it, got it.
Maybe, let's see this here.
Okay, that's clear.
This could be nice.
Fuck yeah.
Oh!
Not battery though.
Damn.
Let me blow you up.
We gained angel chance from that.
Let's go into the curse room.
We're gonna enter via here.
There we go!
Battery achieved, baby!
Huge play right there.
Actually amazing.
We have three re-rolls now.
There it is!
I'm taking it.
Yep.
Wait, we can still, oh, wait, wait, wait, hold on.
No!
Save for the angel, save.
Also, why is it still open?
Shouldn't it be closing?
Do I have something that leaves it open?
Weird.
Maybe it's only after you enter and when you leave.
Then it's gonna close if you leave this room.
Or, I mean, if you leave the demon room.
I think, yeah, that's probably it.
Alright, I think we just move on here.
17 coins, there's nothing else I wanna buy, I don't think, right?
Let me just double check.
Could also blow this up.
But nah.
Wait, down here.
Piggy bank, maybe.
I think I like that!
Let's take it!
Then we take this as well.
I know it may seem like a waste because we're gonna get battery on the next floor.
But think about it like this.
If we find a boss room, like almost immediately on the next floor, we're gonna do the boss, hope for an angel re-roll, come back later after we've cleared some rooms, and after we've gained some more battery, huh?
Not bad.
Go!
Oh yeah.
Don't lose the buffer.
Let's look for that boss room, fast!
Dude, I maneuvered this room like a pro.
Having the good damage definitely helps, though.
Hey, it opened!
I don't know why.
Butt penny!
Focus.
Sweet.
That was a bit risky.
Okay, this guy poops green, that's good to know.
Solid performance.
VRP.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
It says the last pill, but does it really mean my last item in the bottom right?
So I wonder if I do die shard, come back here, and VRP.
If it's going to give me another die shard.
Huh?
I think there may be something to that.
Come on, show me the boss room.
Whoa!
Yo!
Oh no, I can't... I'm not going to be able to see...
Oh, matchstick is actually solid for me.
More bombs, the better.
Yo, that's huge.
The fact that I can't see items on this floor is kind of fucked, because I have the die shard, I got my d6, you know.
Damn, man.
And we even have this... Oh, don't do this to me.
That's so sad.
Yeah, heal me.
Oh, don't push me to the pool!
That's unfair.
Bombs have a 10% chance to spawn a bomb on detonation.
I'm liking that too, to be honest with you.
But I think we're going to keep the one we have.
Look at them creeping around the corner.
Round the corner, round the corner.
Can I somehow finagle my way in there?
I don't think so.
Treasure room!
Oh, we don't know what it is, it's so sad.
Oh shit, don't take my battery.
Even though I don't need it.
No.
I mean, I guess it's fine, right?
It's okay.
Dude, imagine if you have like...
Dammit.
If you have the hourglass, you can walk in and grab the question mark.
And if you don't like it, you revert, come back in.
Take the other question mark, huh?
That's cool.
I could get the battery.
Not that I need it.
I need money, actually.
Kinda want to buy that question mark.
Don't take my useless battery.
Dammit!
Oh, it's not going to empty my entire bar.
I thought it was in, like, everything.
That's nice.
I'm going to get one last charge on that battery before I go in the boss room.
Wait, it doesn't matter.
We can't see what item it is anyway.
Who cares?
Go, my god.
No!
Okay, we gotta take care of these fucking bananas.
God damn, son.
Okay, heal!
Or kill him with the thing.
Shit!
Bomb him!
Yeah.
I took way too much damage in here.
This was a horrible performance.
I even took more damage there.
What a terrible way to do it.
Speedballs, speed and shot speed.
That's good, I like it!
Hey, makes me happy.
I needed a bit of speed.
Felt like I was a bit slow.
Let's keep exploring.
Nineteen coins, you know what that means.
Yoink!
Spider much!
Best question mark of all time!
I can't lose this run now.
This is the best run ever.
Come on, man.
Oh, that is so huge.
Fuck yeah.
Love it.
Oh god, that was...
Oh wait, explosions heal me!
Even those do.
I have to get used to this.
Oh, gimme that.
More money.
Why am I afraid of the bomb guys?
I should be embracing them, literally.
More bombs for me, that's lovely.
You know, I feel like at this point, I may as well go in here.
Wait.
When I hold tab, it says D6 plus D20.
In the bottom right.
What the fuck does that mean?
Hold on.
Reroles all items and...
Oh!
I guess it's...
So it's not...
Oh, okay!
It's not just pedestal items like my D6.
It's everything.
Ah.
Well, shit.
Okay, I guess D20 means normal items then.
Let's go look for secrets.
It's actually kinda nice to know.
Could be here.
Looking good.
Looking real good, actually.
Haha!
Oh my god.
Keyb...
Hey, good thing I didn't spend 60 fucking whatever keys on that, huh?
Now I got my own keybomb.
For free.
That other guy tried to rip me off.
Okay.
Uh...
I think we're done here.
Yeah.
Oh man, this is juicy though.
I could step in there.
Oh wait, he's taking the key!
Okay, fine.
Doesn't spawn a chest for me though.
We're leaving.
Get the hell out of here.
Uh...
I keep the die shard.
We have to remember, we gotta find a teleport card.
This is big.
Any teleport card will do.
Keep it in mind, keep it in mind.
What am I doing?
I totally just blanked.
This is horrible.
Guys, I can't see my HP.
This is not good.
This is really bad.
Oh my god.
Is this the end of this amazing run?
Please, no.
Don't stop the fun now.
I beg you.
At least we can see what items are in this one.
Oh, sci-fi!
I gotta take it.
It's too good.
That is massive.
Dude, this guy's dodging like he's Neo or something.
Very impressive.
The thing is though, I need more red hearts.
This is like a really big problem.
We gotta find health ups.
Shit.
Took my battery.
Oh no, it's a fake shot.
Wait, does he only shoot horizontal?
No, okay.
Whoa, that's actually not bad.
I was considering re-rolling, but I think I like that.
God, I love spider mod.
It's just...
Whoo, beautiful.
Oh god.
Yeah, yeah, come to me.
Say hi to my barrel.
Come here.
Dude, sci-fi is helping so much.
What a bro.
Boss.
Let's do this.
Ooh, that's good.
Nice.
We're taking this.
Holy grail.
Grant's flight.
Absolutely yes.
I'm not even going to consider re-rolling that.
That is unbelievably good.
We got a plus health as well.
I mean, that's just glorious.
Oh, I can fly now.
So let's just go crazy.
I mean, look how my character looks.
I look like...
I'm kind of...
What's that pop singer's name?
The one who has a weird funny name.
Oh man, we can grab these now.
Oh yeah.
Dude.
I spy myself a secret room.
I lied.
I was testing you.
I should have walked in here and seen this.
I guess I'm just checking every room right now, because I now have flying.
There's nothing there.
We have not found a secret room yet.
There's also another room here.
It's an explorer.
We can go into the curse room.
Since we have flying, we're going to take only a little bit of damage.
We can also go in here.
Oh man, there's actually so many options.
Oh my god.
Ah, sci-fi is going to help me against this.
You can't hurt me.
France flight, that's funny.
Teleports to the shop, useless.
I don't know if I should do this, actually.
I think I'd rather save my money for the next shop.
Shiny rock.
Tinted rocks and rocks covering crawl spaces will occasionally gleam.
Ooh, that's nice.
But having the matchstick is going to spawn a lot of bombs for me, which is healing.
Right?
So I think it's actually better.
Yeah.
Then again, this is really good.
I could use this and quickly scan the floor, I guess.
Let's do that.
Occasionally gleam.
Are there even that many rocks?
Oh, maybe here?
I don't see any gleaming going on.
Gleam for me.
Let me see.
I wonder if this counts as like a place where there could be a crawl space underneath.
There's no rocks here either.
Ah, okay.
Fuck it.
I think we're just going to leave.
We're going to grab the teleport and we're going to get out.
Unless... wait, there's still this one I want to destroy.
Nice.
Thank you.
I don't think that was worth it, actually, but you know.
Okay.
We're going.
I realized I should have used the D6 in there, actually, or the...
What do you call it?
You know, to re-roll the... but I couldn't do it.
I don't want to go back in now.
That's fine.
Destroy that.
Here we go.
Let me double check.
A checklist?
Yes.
Yes, we got the D6.
We got the teleport.
I think we're good.
Let's move.
Necropolis.
Wait, why am I shooting so slowly?
Hold on, something's wrong.
Whoa, what's happening here?
It feels like my attack speed just went down.
It's hard to explain, but it just kind of did.
What the fuck?
You can't reach me.
Maybe I'm imagining things.
It felt like it was faster on the last floor.
I think I'm going crazy.
Ahoy.
Ah, I don't like these enemies.
I mean...
Let's do this one first and come back to the other card.
Hmm, I can re-roll that.
What is my lowest stat?
It's probably going to give me luck.
I don't like that.
Let's just re-roll it.
Holy crap!
Best re-roll ever!
No!
How did that happen?
Disappointed!
Oh, wait, these guys are... Ah, they're in there.
You can't leave.
Wait, what is the point of this?
Wait, what if you couldn't fly over rocks?
What would you do here?
So weird.
Fuck!
Nerds.
Also, I'm still instinctively trying to dodge explosions.
Man, I need Norman Reedus.
I need him right now.
Thank you.
Oh, this opened for me.
Well, well, well.
Allow me to introduce myself.
Jesus!
Give me a chance here.
I was looting.
Fly, fly!
My best friend.
Oh, my goodness.
Nice treasure room here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't take my battery!
Thank God.
More range.
It's actually not bad.
And then we have two out of three on spawn.
Could be worth it.
But if I re-roll, I'm going to re-roll two items, right?
So it could be really nice.
Let's see what else I have.
One out of three off.
Sci-fly, which is Beelzebub.
Seraphim.
Spider-baby.
That's it.
I think I'm going to re-roll this.
Blaucoma.
A chance to fire concussive tears to confuse enemy struck.
Mmm.
It seems redheart pickups and drops black.
That's also good.
I don't know.
I don't really need redheart pickups, right?
Because I can heal myself with bombs.
But I don't have that many bombs.
I don't have a solution for my lack of bombs.
I think I'll come back and try and re-roll this again.
I'm going to leave my options open here.
For now.
Here, this guy has a lot of HP.
Laos.
Chance of spawning a blue spider any time I see him in a room with enemies.
No.
Wow, that's cheap!
Dude!
I got to take that one.
The bottle of pills.
At this point, we got to get a health up right from this.
Power.
That's sick!
Wait, VRRP.
That's going to give me 48-hour energy, right?
So, I take this.
I use VRRP.
Let me just double-read this.
Spawns.
Oh, that's kind of sick.
Oh, dude.
Holy shit!
Wow!
Dude!
We can re-roll this forever.
Bomb friend.
Poison tears.
Whoa.
Maybe?
Let me just do it one more time.
Virgo!
Wait, if I take this...
Hold on a minute.
Did I have that mask on the last run?
Or was it this run?
No, dude, dude.
I...
This...
I need that.
I'm going to have such crazy survival.
Think about it.
I have mask.
I have the poor man's...
Freaking...
What is it called?
You know what I mean?
The...
I can't find it.
Goddammit.
I don't know.
We have sci-fi as well, right?
To help.
We also got the one where we take less damage per hit.
Let's grab this one.
Let me grab the one up health here as well.
Shit.
Dammit.
Oh well.
It's okay.
I'll buy a key.
We gotta keep this on us.
The hermit is very important.
Kind of want to use another battery on the pills.
Let's wait a bit.
These guys are not going to explode.
They're going to explode into a little...
Dude, this guy is shooting fast.
Petrified poop.
What do I have before?
A shiny rock.
No.
Oh, wait.
I forgot to change it out.
Unless this was the same floor.
Oh...
Shit.
I didn't mean to keep this.
This spider is going to annoy me.
Oh!
Bop!
Oh man, I got hit.
Whoa!
Tear up!
Oi!
Let's go for the boss.
We can maybe re-roll.
And then we're going to teleport out.
We have the hermit.
Let me just double check.
It is the teleport.
Here we go.
Boom!
Oh wait, it's not mom!
That's next floor.
Fuck!
I got confused.
I thought this was it.
Actually, I like that.
More chances to get powerful.
Sci-fly is amazing.
It may actually be S tier.
I would have gotten hit there, you know?
Stabler.
I don't...
No!
We need more HP.
You know what?
I need attack speed.
Two extra soul hearts?
Not bad.
I'm actually taking that.
Attack speed is one of the bigger things I need right now.
Yeah.
Me likey.
Give me that.
Also, I haven't seen this glow anyway.
The gleam.
More bombs.
I'm going to blow this.
No, I'm not going to blow this guy.
Sharp keys are going to give me five keys, but it's not worth...
Unless...
No.
It's not part of a package deal.
I could...
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, I could have grabbed this battery and re-rolled again.
I forgot about it.
But I mean, I'm happy with my current item.
I'm happy with the item that I got.
Very happy.
I love it, actually.
I could maybe find a secret here.
Okay.
I can definitely go in here.
Dang it.
Perthrow.
Dude.
Health up.
Damn it.
Maybe I'll come back for Perthrow.
Oh, no.
Without Sci-fly, this room would have taken three health off me.
Wait, what?
No, no.
I wasted a key.
I need more bombs.
Like, bombs is the...
Like, if I can get like 20 bombs or 30 bombs, then this run is pretty much good.
Like, I'm good, you know?
That is the main thing I need.
Yeah, let's leave.
We're done here.
No, no, no.
Then again, what was this?
He's spawning a blue spider.
Nah.
Boring.
I could use Perthrow in the shop, I guess, but...
Nah.
Let's move on.
You know what?
Maybe I'll take this.
Let's look for some gleaming rocks.
I don't see any here.
Maybe some here.
Moving on.
Okay, this is the one with mom.
Oh, we can't see the map.
Shit.
Walnut.
Wait, being hit by an explosion has a 33% chance of destroying the trinket and sp...
I mean, wait.
Uh...
I like it.
I'm gonna get hit by explosions anyway, on purpose.
Wow, two batteries here.
Aha!
Bastard.
Jesus Christ.
Alright, this is an insane room.
Thank God for sci-fi.
I'm also lost already.
Hey, arcade.
Not yet.
Oh, no, not this.
Yeah!
But oh!
Wait, the bosses...
I think we should just go for it.
Yeah?
Mom?
What the hell?
Why was I shooting so slowly?
My attack speed is low again.
Okay, I mean, I'm nailing it.
Good shit, good shit, good shit.
We even have a demon room.
I may actually go in there.
Oh, uh...
I think I'll re-roll, actually.
I'm not feeling it.
Then again, we are reaching the point where the D6 may not be worth it anymore.
No, it is actually worth it, because we're gonna go through some stages...
where we can potentially get items, right?
Yeah.
Okay, here we go.
That's a lot of money.
But can I spend it?
That's the question.
Oh, that was a bit close.
Naughty.
I have no idea where I am.
We're just gonna have to fumble around in the dark.
Until we find what we're looking for.
Now, 66 coins.
May as well do some gambling.
I need bombs from this.
This is the main thing.
There we go.
Also, how do we have .22 luck?
What a weird number.
How do you even get there?
No!
The gambling god said no.
Okay, maybe it's not worth it to spend these bombs on that.
I didn't go this way yet.
Oh, god.
I ran into him.
Uh-oh.
Five?
Let me see.
Oh, wait.
If I do that, I wonder if I get to keep my thing I used already.
My teleport.
I think it's too risky.
I can't risk this.
I don't know if I'm gonna keep it.
I'm not gonna do it, otherwise I would.
I totally would.
I can't risk this.
Nice.
I will say, though, I feel like my DPS is not that great.
It's not, like, mind-blowingly good.
It's decent, you know, but it's not super great.
And I feel like we need super great for what we're trying to do in this run.
Survival is good, but my damage is lacking.
Ooh, check this out!
Yo!
Ha-ha!
Wait, oh, okay.
What are the chills of that?!
What the fuck?!
Hell yeah!
Oh, I shouldn't have... maybe I should have picked it up.
The compass.
Uh... oh, wait, Bible.
Ooh!
Wait, this is all very exciting.
But, ah, man, it's gonna cost me red hearts.
Shit.
Allows two trinkets.
No.
I'm gonna donate all my money, man, and then we're just gonna YOLO.
I could also re-roll, actually.
Wow!
Donated a lot.
Black candle.
Immunity to floor curses, immunity to negative effects from certain items.
Increases chance of encountering...
Doubles the amount of pickups.
Doubles the damage of familiars, increases their...
Ah, nah.
Makes one item in the shop or devil room free.
No.
I think this one, if anything.
So it says immunity to negative effects from certain items.
I wonder what that could be.
Wait, what could that be?
Do I have any negative effects right now?
With my items?
What would a negative effect be?
I can't even think of a single item that has a negative effect.
But, ah...
Immunity to...
No, I don't think any of this is worth it.
We gotta go.
I... Imagine if I jump down the hole.
Holy shit.
I almost did it.
Wait, what is happening here?
Health up!
Fuck.
Haha, 90 degree turns.
Actually, I like it.
Now, where the hell is this door?
Oh, there it is.
Wait, am I done here?
I'm not.
I am.
Let's leave.
Uh...
I can't see the map, so I don't know if I missed something.
Maybe I did.
I don't know.
Where's it gonna go for it?
Wish me luck!
Here we go.
Mausulium.
Dude, the 90 degree turns are kinda killer here.
What the...
Dude, it's calmed down.
More bombs?
It's massive.
Hahaha!
That's awesome.
Another teleport.
Let's do this.
The moon.
Oh, dude, I'm totally gonna blow that up.
No, I'm not.
I don't need any hearts.
I feel like with this trinket, I can just sort of shoot and...
I'm gonna hit something.
It's not quite as good as homing tears, but it's like almost.
That's good, you know?
Oh,
it's not that good.
Maybe it's like 20% as good as homing tears.
Dude, here's the boss.
I think I'm gonna keep going to potentially get stronger before I do.
I'm in a pretty strong position here to get stronger.
Even stronger, I mean.
Clean.
Surgical.
Go south.
I feel a sneeze coming.
Wow.
The sneeze came.
Oh, dude, destroy these fucking things.
Okay, I kinda hit my trinket.
We need another one.
It's not gonna cut it.
Come here!
This room is so annoying!
Is there another one?
Oh, there.
Jesus.
Masterful.
Uh, death?
Yeah, why not?
Oh!
Uh, no!
We're gonna re-roll!
Wandering harbinger familiar that spawns locusts and deals with the familiar ships.
I mean, sure.
Not that great.
Would've loved something else, but, you know.
Whoa!
There's three choices!
Contagion.
Uh...
Maybe...
Kinda wanna come back and re-roll.
Yeah.
I'm gonna come back and re-roll.
Gee, oh my god.
I got whipped.
Go in here.
Wait, fully re-ch- Oh!
Hey!
What's this?
Well, dude, hold on.
Damn!
Uh, don't pick them up.
Wait, hold on.
If I re-roll...
It's not gonna re-stock the already taken items, right?
Like, if I take all four, it's not gonna give me four new.
We're gonna experiment with that, but first, we go back and re-roll.
Whoa, what is this?
I don't care about that.
This is definitely some sort of familiar.
It's like a little turd or a little... one of those things that come out of the ground, you know?
I don't know, man.
I feel like I gotta re-roll to something I'm familiar with and no.
Ooh, wait!
Stigmata!
It's actually... I mean, it's one more red heart.
I'm thinking... the reason I'm thinking this is good...
is because the more red hearts I have, the better my bomb healing's gonna be, right?
Because I'm gonna get to heal more.
But then again, it's only half a heart per bomb, so it's not that great.
This is too health, but I lose speed, which is kind of important.
I'm gonna re-roll again.
I'm gonna re-roll until I get the best item that I can possibly get from there.
Because I can get these batteries, I can take the pill, get more batteries... I can go crazy with this.
I have so many options.
Dude, you know what I should do?
Let's find a secret room and re-roll in there, if there's an item, of course.
I have changed my plan.
Plans haven't changed.
We can also go step, maybe?
We can step a little bit.
No, it's not needed.
There's no reason to.
So we found one secret room already.
I have 11 bombs, but I kinda... Actually, my bombs are not that great for healing.
Because it is only like half a heart.
It's not gonna be that important.
I mean, I'm gonna have to just completely gamble here.
Wait, let me check the other examples I have here.
I'm not seeing any pattern here at all.
Okay, maybe that the white one is more centralized?
You see that?
The gray one is more sort of off, outwards from the center?
Maybe.
Let's try and use that logic.
So maybe... Actually, we haven't even explored everything.
How about we do that first?
Oh my god, guys.
Calm down, calm down.
What do you want?
Oh, his brain is over here.
Dude!
Scary.
Envy.
Yep.
What's that?
That's an increase to all stats when health, active items at full... Ooh, I mean, that's pretty much all the time for me.
I like this.
I like that.
That's good.
Maybe I'll do... Dude, what about right here?
That's very far away.
Shit.
I may just go back and reroll that treasure room, honestly.
It's too much of a longshot what I'm doing here.
Let's try here.
No.
Yeah, it's not gonna happen.
Wait, why is the boss room... Oh, we haven't done the boss yet, right?
Makes sense.
Yeah, treasure room.
Let's see what we can scrounge up in there.
Fuck of s... No.
No.
Oh, this is... No!
Boring.
Reroll again.
Um... This one.
Sick.
I just will pick that up.
BBF.
Explode some contact!
That could be really good for me.
That's gonna heal me.
But it's not like... So imagine I'm at the last boss, right?
And this guy's gonna be fucking DVD logoing around the edges.
Like, I'm gonna have to pay attention to that while I dodge projectiles.
I don't think it's gonna happen, man.
I gotta be honest.
I know.
I'm gonna keep rolling.
It's just not good enough.
This is my last reroll.
Come on, baby.
Come on!
Okay, I don't know what this is.
Let's take it.
The peeper.
Blop!
Bounces around the room and deals con... increases damage of tears fired from... Whoa!
Okay!
That's actually not bad!
That actually amplifies my shit quite a bit.
Nice!
I mean, I'm happy with that.
39 coins left.
Maybe I can...
What's this?
The high priestess?
Isn't that the one with the mom's foot stomps down?
Let me try and reroll.
No way!
It rerolls everything!
Oh my god!
Okay, well, in that case... This is actually not worth it.
Blue flies and spiders do double damage?
Okay!
No way!
What's that?
Bosses drop two items.
That's maybe too late for that glowing hourglass.
Ooh, that could be really good!
Maybe we say goodbye to the D6 at this point.
And switch it up for the hourglass.
I think I like that!
We're going to take this... If I now grab this and reroll, it's going to reroll the hourglass.
Wait, I wonder, is this going to reroll my D6 then?
Hold on.
No, it's not.
Okay, good, good.
Health down?
Yeah, right.
Blank card triggers the effect of the card.
Health without consuming it.
Not feeling that.
Maybe bomb?
No, it's not worth
it.
Come on, one more.
Sure, that's fine.
Okay, we're going to blow these fools up.
Oh, right, okay.
This guy is never spawning a chest, by the way.
Have you noticed?
Not once has he done it.
This little fucker has been unbelievably useless.
He's consumed so many keys.
Done nothing for me.
Whoops.
We're leaving.
Checklist.
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, go.
Here we go.
Time for the ascension.
Ascender with gorb.
My damage is shit.
This is the big problem we have.
Survival good, damage bad.
I wonder if each of these ascension floors count as a floor in terms of the hourglass.
For example, right now I took damage, right?
Let me do this.
We're going to test.
Motherfucker!
Okay, fine, whatever.
Crazy room.
Is there even any points to just exploring here right now?
Because I don't have the Black Bible or anything where I can gain HP like last time.
I think I'm just going to ascend.
Let's see if I get the three charges on the hourglass.
I do, okay.
That's good to know.
I'm going to undo all mistakes now.
Whoa, wait, whoa, whoa, hold on.
There's items.
I think I want this.
Man, fuck, I should have kept my d6.
What the hell?
Faster shot, yeah, that's good.
We've got to explore them.
I mean, if there's stuff like that here,
I simply can't pass it up.
Wait, did it say Spectral Cheer Sprites?
It's got to be painful, man.
I don't find damage.
Come on, health up.
Speed up, shot speed.
No, I don't like... Oh, I should have reversed!
Too late, dammit.
Too late.
He's self-destructive and disturbed just like his father.
Look at who he has to look up to.
And you're drunk again, aren't you?
Shut up, Max.
Shut up.
Just keep pushing me like this.
I'm leaving.
Good.
Leave.
We'll be fine without you.
Abandon us like you've abandoned yourself.
Oh my god.
That may actually be okay, because I am leaving creep.
Which creep is it?
And which one does it?
I think it's one of the familiars.
Oh god, I will never be able to find this.
This one!
Enemies that touch the cloud have a chance to be struck by a damaging light beam!
I like it!
You know what, I should be bombing this.
Every health I can get right now.
Oh, he's dead, okay.
I got the chariot as well.
It's like my panic button.
Dude, can we not literally just retry the final boss with this fucking hourglass?
Like, if shit goes really bad and we're like at one HP, I can just reverse, come back, try again.
That's crazy.
What?
I fucking ran into a spiky rock.
That is unbelievable.
That is actually the worst.
That's painful.
Wow.
I should have reversed!
I keep forgetting that I have it.
Hurts extra bad afterwards when you realize.
Thank you, sci-fi.
I appreciate it.
Oh my god.
Okay, here we go, ascension, but wait, wait, wait.
Reverse!
Try again.
Good.
And there's one room left, we gotta do.
Wait, what is doing so much damage?
Is it my guy on the horse?
Size of Isaac's fart is increased.
No thanks.
Let me see the guy on the horse again.
Where are you, buddy?
That one.
Shifts form every 10 seconds.
Each form spawns locusts with a unique trait.
I think this guy may be better than I think.
I think he's gonna help me out quite a bit.
Holy HP.
That was crazy.
That's such a cool effect.
Oh, that's interesting.
I even have some coins.
Come on.
Don't be greedy.
Sci-fly.
Nice.
Oh, we're done.
This floor is big.
Wait, what is that one?
Is that a golden one or it looks different?
Oh, okay, it is.
It looked like, I don't know, like a more beige poop.
Not so much golden.
It's just a colored palette here.
Okay, we can ascend now or do one more.
Rainbow.
Why not?
We're done?
We're done.
Come on, man.
Come on.
Basement two.
Reverse.
You know what?
Just stand inside the rocks and shoot, man.
This is the strategy.
Blade safe.
Do we have tinted rocks here?
Not seeing any.
Battery.
I
love just camping inside the rocks.
Fragmented card.
New floors will gen... I think that's useless now.
That's not gonna do much for me.
Unless it actually generates new secret rooms on these floors as well, which could be kind of cool.
I'm so happy that I'm flying.
It helps so much.
Not yet.
One more room.
I'm getting good at dealing with those guys.
Hey, look, one of these.
Alright, let's leave.
This is... Now we go on caves one.
No, basement one.
Okay.
So I think this is... I can still use my hourglass here.
Wow.
Dad.
I miss you.
Don't leave me.
Yeah, this Harbinger guy is doing a lot of work.
As usual for me now.
Dude, I'm so anxious.
I think we can do it even with this setup here.
Like the damage is not there, but we have a lot of retries, assuming it actually works with the hourglass.
And I feel like as long as I get to try a bunch of times and learn the patterns and all that, I think we got it.
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
We couldn't ascend now if we want to, but...
I haven't really seen any other items here.
I saw this one room on one of these floors that had an item, but...
Maybe it's because I missed that room on the way here.
Where are you?
Sick.
Wait, the Empress.
That's good.
Damage and speed.
What's the other one?
No.
Yeah, definitely the Empress.
We want to keep that.
That's huge.
That's so big for me right now.
Oh, spectral tears for the wind.
We got one room left to explore.
Okay, let's get out.
I think it was over here-ish, no?
Shit.
Here?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Here we go.
Home.
Ah,
I should have let him pick up the key.
That was bad.
Yeah.
Mom's wig.
Firing has a chance to spawn blue spiders?
Sure.
I mean, it's very stylish.
Okay, let's do this.
I gotta save all my hourglasses for the last boss.
Not this one, the last boss.
Unless it goes really bad.
We'll see.
Here we go.
Wait, damage is actually not that bad?
Whoa.
Oh, God.
Oh, shit.
Okay, here we go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
Hey, that was bad.
Oh, okay.
We gotta retry this.
One more time.
Come on.
That's the last one.
We're gonna save the rest for the last boss.
I feel like it's difficult for me to deal damage against this guy with my current- Oh, my God.
Really?
I walked into him.
I'm gonna bomb, actually.
I'm gonna bomb this TV.
Fuck you.
Stay at range.
Sci-fly working overtime.
Good.
Okay, good, good.
He's gonna charge me now with something.
Yeah, there he comes, okay.
Good damage.
He's dealing good damage here.
Solid.
Okay, not bad, not bad.
I like it, I like it.
Bring it on.
Skip.
Wait, my hourglass is different.
Hold on, what happened?
After three uses, it instead uses the hourglass effect.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
So, what is this?
Reminds time and- I don't know what the hourglass effect is!
Standard hourglass- I don't know what the standard hourglass effect is.
I'm fucked.
I'm gonna try it.
Just slows time, right?
Okay, well, that's good.
For the entire room?
Yo.
I should have saved it.
Fuck.
That was a waste.
I fucked up!
Okay, my damage is not that bad.
Okay.
Dude, solid so far!
Oh, wait, the bombs are gonna fall to the floor.
Oh, shit.
Oh, don't stand in the poison.
Kill the little guy.
Whatever this is, kill it.
Oh my god, Sci-fly, I love you.
Stay low, so we can actually dodge.
Good, good, good.
Kill this guy.
Dodging time.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Good.
Dude, Sci-fly is helping so much, it's crazy.
Wait, we can slow time again!
Dude.
Watch this.
I'm gonna time it.
Yeah, you saw the bomb land on him!
Yeah, it's horizontal, horizontal.
Up, yep.
Okay, okay.
Fuck you, fuck you, we're gonna drop bombs on you.
Carbon bombing, motherfucker.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Bomb you, bomb you.
Come on, nerds!
Let's fucking do this!
I forgot what you do, I forgot what you do.
Slow time!
Drop bombs.
Fuck you.
Okay, dodge that, good.
Bomb for you.
Easy.
Come on, come on, come on.
Bring it on, son.
Fuck you!
There's more?
Oh, fuck.
We got slow time again.
Uh, what's happening here?
Oh shit, oh, flabby birds!
Oh my god.
He's gonna fall?
Okay.
Shit, I can't get out!
Take me, what's happening?
Oh my god.
Whoa!
I have no more bombs.
Okay, okay.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Holy crap, that was close.
Where are you?
What's happening?
Uh, all right.
That's fine, whatever.
No!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Oh shit.
Okay, okay, we're doing this again.
I got you, I got you.
I got you.
Shit.
Dude, he has so much HP.
Flabby birds!
Flap them wings, bitch!
Oh my god.
Up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Damage is decent, I guess.
Focus, focus, focus.
Hold, hold, hold, hold!
Come on, come on!
Fucking kill it!
Dude, how long does this go on for?
Come on.
Can we do it?
Yes!
Okay,
let's do it.
Cuppy!
Oh, nice!
What?
No!
Oh, that's the beginning of the game!
Oh my god!
It was dad telling us a story!
That's kind of fucked up, man.
Oh, Jesus loves you.
He loves you so much.
Dude, everything about this game is just so sad.
I wish I could just hug Isaac, you know?
Tell him everything's gonna be okay and take him under my wing and give him a good upbringing.
It's just so incredibly sad.
Man, that's so sad.
He's imagining what his childhood could have been like on his way up.
Terrible.
Everything jar has appeared.
Okay, okay, okay.
Well, let's call it there, guys.
We're doing a shorter stream tonight.
It's kind of late for me.
I just needed to get my fix, you know?
I had to get my fix.
That was a successful one.
Short and successful.
That's what I would call that one.
Sorry about that.
Blowing your ears off.
Wow.
There we go.
Blue streak is over, damn right.
What do you say to that, huh?
Finally did it.
That was the third attempt.
Third time's the charm.
Good work, Oliver.
Now the streak goes up.
Stonks go up, you're right.
Finally, win streak.
Win streak of one.
I forgot what character I was playing.
Oh yeah, I was playing Eden.
Yeah.
That run was so long, I totally forgot what I started with.
Guys, I did so well on that last boss, too.
I was shaking, I was crying, I was pooping and puking when I figured out that there was another phase.
I thought I was done after the fourth one.
I really, I really was like, fuck.
The white hair is always a dead giveaway when you're Eden.
Oh, I see.
I should look out for that, then.
We were all shitting and fitting together.
Now I'm imagining a bunch of people in one room just group shitting all at the same time.
That's horrible.
That's a horrible picture.
Yeah, maybe don't imagine that, you're right.
Mostly pissing, actually.
Okay.
The only time you can be happy when you know you have cancer is nice.
That's true.
To be honest, it's kind of nice that you didn't have that much more damage so you get to see all the moves.
I guess.
You're right.
So if I actually end up with more damage, I guess I could have skipped some of those if I was fast enough.
But yeah, that was a roller coaster, man.
That last fight had me on the edge of my seat.
My heart was shaking.
My hands are shaking.
Yeah, sci-fi was fucking MVP as well.
Sci-fi and having the poor man's wafer.
I had that one.
Or was that last run I had?
Did I have wafer this run or the poor man's wafer?
It was cancer, right?
Yeah, okay, okay.
It was cancer.
Good.
Good, good, good.
Yeah, I had that.
I had sci-fi.
I had the mask as well.
Like, it was just fantastic.
Pyromaniac, yes.
You know what's funny?
I was planning my entire build around using bombs at the very end towards the very last boss here to heal myself.
That was my whole game plan from the first floor when I had that.
I was like, oh, here we go.
Let's fucking go.
But it turned out you couldn't even do that because the bombs fall from the sky, right?
So that turned out to be not the plan.
Yeah, and I used them on the horseman.
You follow the script to the letter, you should have a race.
I know.
You like that?
He's nodding, he's nodding.
Okay, okay.
I missed a couple cool things that should have happened in the script, but you know, it turned out well.
That last face was really cool though, right?
It was!
I think it's super awesome that it turned into this sort of 2D flabby bird side-scroller thing.
Imagine if you had converter, right?
You know what, actually, I don't think converter would have been super good this run.
I will admit that on this run.
Maybe it wouldn't have done too much.
Actually, now that I think about it, I could have turned all my stuff into red hearts and healed myself with bombs falling from the sky.
Like, I can probably just stand on top of the boss and bomb myself, but it's a little risky.
Converter slander will not be tolerated.
I mean, don't get me wrong, it is like a fucking S-tier item.
But it's just hindsight, right?
I did everything without it and so maybe I wouldn't have changed anything just because it worked out the way it did it.
Blasphemy against the holy converter.
I mean, the converter is freaking holy.
The only thing that's bad about the converter is in the very beginning of the game.
Because you want to have a buffer, right?
To maintain your angel status and demon status and all that.
So if you convert everything in the beginning, then you have a higher chance of getting hits on the red hearts, so it's bad.
So you want to have a balance, right?
We need a tier list of the items Oliver has discovered.
You know what, we can do that.
Should we make a tier list next time?
That's a great idea, Meep's Kitten.
We can do like a 30-minute tier list before the stream next time.
We're going to go through all the items I've unlocked.
I'm going to go into the menu and, you know, just scroll through them.
There's 700 plus items.
Yeah, but I have... I don't have all that, right?
How many days?
We haven't had a Bethany run.
Oliver, do a Beth run.
Oliver, do a Beth run, please!
I don't like Bethany very much, but maybe we'll give her another shot.
Right now, I'm on a very long win streak and I can't risk that by playing Bethany, okay?
I need to pick the good characters.
We're going to maintain this insane streak.
Hey, look, in my book, it's a very long win streak.
Do a baked potato.
How would I do that?
Sounds like some kind of move.
Lilith.
You mean, you mean Eulith, right?
I feel like Lilith is hard to say for me as a Danish person.
I also have a slight stammer, which is not very apparent because I've trained it away.
But I do have a stammer and I have, like, ways to circumvent it you don't know about.
But I do have a stammer.
But Lilith, for me, is hard to say.
Eulith is much easier for me to say.
Thought on the last boss, I loved it.
I think it's cool.
I really enjoy going up and down.
I like the flabby bird thing.
You're so cool, Oliver.
So are you, put a little.
You're also cool.
How were you meant to escape the sock from the big boss?
I don't know.
I turned on the slowdown.
And then it seemed I was able to get out.
But it definitely looked like his sock was too strong.
Yeah, too low speed, for sure.
Favorite floor thematically?
Oh...
I really love... Downpour.
Yeah.
I think there's just something about that place.
The atmosphere is impeccable.
When it rains, it downpours.
Exactly.
Did you know where the rains, when it rains, it pours where it comes from?
You probably don't.
I know, because I watched the YouTube video recently, telling me what it is.
You may think it's something to do with priests and religious people.
Exactly, Baconator.
It is Morton Salt.
I forget the exact reason, though.
It's something to do with the fact that you pour the salt when it rains.
Because I forgot the exact reason there, but yeah.
Sorry, I can't enlighten you.
I thought I could.
I just remembered, I don't remember.
But it is related to salt.
Salt in America, and it's something to do with people having this giant growth on their head.
And the salt contains iodine that help reduce that sickness.
I mean, you can... Yeah, sorry about that.
I got your shit up, for no reason.
Because Morton Salt doesn't stick together when it wets, so it still pours.
I think that's it, yeah.
That's it.
I've played Dead Space, GW and Johnny.
I want to.
I saw they remastered the first one, so are there plans to remaster the other ones?
Because I kind of want to play them all remastered, I guess, if I could.
Hey, thank you for the sub, Gemini.
You deserve this sub for beating that boss.
I appreciate it.
I'm proud of myself as well.
I feel like I played really well today.
Have you watched Project Hail Mary yet?
I actually... have.
I was hesitating a little bit, because I'm missing 20% of the movie.
I watched 80% of it.
I need 20%, the last 20%, because I got distracted and I had to do something else at the time.
Yeah.
But so far, I'm loving it.
Really cool movie.
Really digging it.
So, you know, I will say I have watched it, but I really haven't.
Yeah, I'm gonna go watch it after this.
I'm gonna get some food and then watch it.
And I know, it's like breaking a cardinal rule, pausing a movie.
Trust me, I am the first guy to say that.
Pausing a movie in my book is almost like a crime.
You can't do that.
You gotta watch the whole thing, it's one experience.
And I broke that rule, it happened.
Something came up in my life while I was watching.
So yeah.
Don't check your email and watch the last 20%.
I doubt people will spoil that.
That's crazy.
If that happens, I'm gonna be surprised.
This song slaps, doesn't it?
Once again, GoldenEye64, baby.
It has all the bangers.
You should repet that with five Bethany runs.
Okay, fine.
I'll do a Bethany run next time.
You convinced me.
I shall do it.
The exact song name is, I can tell you.
It's Damn from GoldenEye.
It's actually the first level in GoldenEye.
Damn.
D-A-M.
Enjoy.
Okay, I'm gonna go guys.
Thank you so much for watching.
This was a massive success.
Great, short, and sweet stream.
Really like those.
Thanks for showing up for it.
This was a blast.
Have a wonderful Tuesday, and I'll see you in the next stream.
Bye-bye.